Aarti Khuntia

Senior account executive



Cuttack, Odisha



+91.8318597448



aartikhuntia640@gmail.com



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:-

- Tally 9.0 ERP, Quick books-desktop and online version, share point, SAP
- Ms-word, Ms-Excel etc.
- Knowledge of portal catalyst system,IQN navigator, beeline-pontoon, field-glass, Job diva, V-channel, ceipal, and ultimatix
- Knowledge of Sales- Tax, TDS, and Filing ITR

STRENGTH:-

- ➤Positive attitude , hardworking, multitasking
- ➤ Ability to reach goals.
- >Leader Quality.
- >Always willing to put extra bit of effort into any assignment.
- ➤ Ability to concentrate for long period of time, willingness to confront difficult problems and the will to perform under pressure.

ATTRIBUTES/ ABILITIES:-

- >Excellent Interpersonal & communication
- ➤ Self-motivated, Methodical & Process drivers
- >A team Player, continue Learner & Proactive.
- ➤Independent & willing to take the Initiative.



Listening to music, Dance, Travelling and Reading



Піпаі

English

Oriya



To gain experience in the field of accounting & utilize my skills, in order to increase productivity of organization and individual growth. Ambitious to build a career in accounting & finance with an organization where team work is required & hardworking is appreciated and to be in position which is but suited to my knowledge & skills.

EDUCATION

Finance, Master of Commerce, Completed, March 2017

Subharti University
Subharti University – Marks 70%, Division I
LUCKNOW, Uttar Pradesh

Business Management, Banking, Accounts, Statistics, Bachelor of Commerce,

Completed, June 2012

Lucknow university

University of Lucknow - Marks 50%, Division II

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Commerce, Intermediate, Completed, June 2009

Lucknow model public college UP BOARD – Marks 69%, Division I Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

COMMERCE, High School, Completed, June 2007

Lucknow model public inter college UP BOARD – Marks 64%, Division I Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

WORK EXPERIENCE

September 2012 - March 2013

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Stock trader

Raj Investment Point (Share marketing)

- · Maintained trading data on spreadsheets for prospective, research, risks.
- Managed both day-to-day, discussing market news, reading
- stock journals, Examining stock performance.

May 2013 - September 2013

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Account Assistant

Bansal & company (Worked in a C.A Firm)

- Maintain day to day books of Accounts in F.A software.
- Maintain Bank Reconcilation Statement and Reconcilation of Debtors & Creditors.
- Maintain Internal Audit: Store And Accounts Book.
- Maintain Journal Entry Sale, Purchase & Exp Invoice.

April 2015 - March 2016

Bengaluru, Karnataka

Lower division clerk

Kendriya Vidyalaya No.1 (School)

- Entries and Maintaining cash book.
- Audit reports, preparing GPF/NPS/CPF account.
- TDS, Enrolment List, Entries of bills, and all kinds official letters.

May 2016 - March 2017

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Account assistant

Angraj Group of Companies (Construction co.)

- Maintain all Accounting voucher entry.
- Maintain timely and accurate account reconciliations.
- Maintain Petty Cash Book & Internal Audit: Store and Accounts Book.
- Maintain day to day Accounts & reporting to the senior management.
- Calculate Sale Tax, Service Tax & TDS, Input & Out put Tax Return.



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthday 24/03/19<u>92</u>

Gender

Female

Father's Name

Mr. Anant kishore khuntia

Nationality Indian

Address

New Rausapatna Gopabandhu Vihar Cuttack - 753001 Odisha April 2017 - January 2019

Finance executive

Sahara Pure eatables corp.Ltd.

- Maintain of all type accounting vouchers entry of different companies.
- Maintain bank reconciliation Statement and Reconciliation of Debtors & Creditors.
- Maintain books of accounts in Tally.
- Maintain payroll information by collecting, calculating, entering data.
- Prepares reports by compiling summaries of earnings, deductions, leave, disability, and nontaxable wages.

March 2019 - Current

Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Senior account executive

Next Level Business Services, Inc. (Us-finance)

- Verifying and approving the time sheets for payments of the consultants working overseas.
- Efficiently track and manage time sheets to streamline payroll and project management.
- Managing invoicing by helping the team in timely invoicing, tracking payment received and payment due.
- Managing billing, collections, and reporting activities according to specific deadlines
- Monitor consultants account details for non-payments, delayed payments and other irregularities.
- Maintaining tracker sheets to track overdue invoices.
- Working with the vendors/clients/consultants on getting the necessary approvals in order to proceed with the payments.
- Handling client escalations.
- Regular follows ups with the vendor/Consultants via mails or calls and getting the missing requisites, in case of any discrepancy.
- Maintaining the data based on the information received.
- Sharing the data with the billing and payments team for smooth and timely processing.
- Streamlined the payment verification process, resulting in improved efficiency and reduced errors.
- Collaborated with the finance team to analyze payment discrepancies and resolve them in a timely manner.



If, I am given the chance to serve under your kind control I assure you use my best capacity for your satisfaction.

Cuttack, Odisha
04/11/2023